They trimmed but Morgan Stanley is
also carrying an overweight stance on it.
Now Kunal Sir, I would like to know your view.
After the report of HDFC Life brokerages, what is the view being formed on the charts now?
Look, the chart is good Neha. If you
see overall, the stock is consolidating in a range
and
it has support around the 200 day moving average. So
in my opinion, one should hold by keeping a stop loss around 620.
I
think HDFC Life is getting ready to touch the levels of 700 again
and at these levels it
appears to be a very safe stock. So
in my opinion, by keeping a small stop loss,
those who have investments can definitely stay invested. New purchases can
also be made at these levels with a stop loss of 620.
So, you
can see a big action on HDFC Life. Should I follow it in IT?